Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real?
Through it all, through
all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
Big Bro won!
I've got Barker's fallen!
Nojiko, is all of this really happening?
Surely this is a dream.
Good job, Luffy!
You almost did as good as me!
Let's face it, I'm pretty much the star,
but I'll cheer for you
anyway because I'm super
modest and I don't want
to steal your thunder!
You really had us going there, Luffy.
Start dealing with the bad guys quicker.
I almost had a heart attack.
You rubber jerk
This is awesome!
Okay, hold it right there!
Damn, it's him!
What a lucky day today is!
Very nice, I saw the entire
fight and I must say good work!
I can only assume that your victory
here was some sort of bizarre accident I
never thought the fishman would lose to
riff-raff like you and your crew However,
now that our long is out of the picture.
I'll be taking all the money I
was supposed to give to him in
addition to all the treasure and
all on park now drop your weapons!
Colonel News me of branch
16 gets all the credit.
Trying to rain these people's
parade now that's just plain?
You scum, just try it.
He'll be sorry.
I promise you that.
He's still talking?
This is for shooting Nojiko.
And also for mercilessly destroying
Bellomere's Tangerine Orchard.
Colonel!
Thanks, Nami.
That felt good.
A thousand more and we'll call it even!
What you're gonna do is
clean up after those fishmen.
Then you're gonna help to
rebuild the town of Gosa,
and you won't lay a finger on any of
the money or valuables in Arlong Park.
That's the island's money now. Got it?
Yeah, right, yeah.
I don't really think you say.
And there's one more thing.
Give me my money back, jerk!
I promise, I promise.
I'll give every berry back.
I'll get you, you pirates!
Luffy is your captain, right?
Well, mark my frigging words, Rubberman!
Major things are gonna happen!
because you made me angry.
I swear you'll regret this.
I'll get my revenge just to wait and see.
Major things are going to happen.
Yeah, how does he know I'm
going to be king of the pirates?
That's not what he means at all.
Are you really that dumb?
Hold on, what next?
Are we in super big trouble or what?
Hey, hey, what do we do?
Hey, everyone, now's not the
time to keep this to ourselves.
We need to tell everyone on the
island what happened here today.
Ahhhh!
Island Park has fallen!
Hey, Zoro!
What's that on your chest? Huh?
Made you look.
What are you joking?
Good job, Nami.
To think our island would
be saved by unruly pirates.
The world is strange.
Why are you still here, Nami?
Your friends have been looking for you.
Hey, Nojiko? Huh? Lorenzo,
if Bellomere were still alive
and I wanted to become a pirate,
do you think she'd let me do it?
A pirate?
What do you think?
Of course she'd never
let her precious daughter
go out to sea with a bunch
of treacherous pirates.
Yeah, she'd let me do it.
But if she had said no, that
wouldn't stop you, would it?
Hmm, that's right. Nope.
I see.
What's up, Genzo?
You certainly are Bellamy's kids.
Oh, yeah.
Nami, you've already made
up your mind about this.
There's no use fighting it.
Live your life.
He's still at it.
Well, you saw the way he
looked after that fight.
Yeah.
Anyone else would have been dead.
You dumbass.
Did you think this would heal on its own?
Seriously, pirates are supposed
to be smarter than this.
Don't you have a ship, Doctor? Doctor?
Never thought of that.
Good idea. Luffy.
But we need to get a
musician first, right?
Why's that?
Because pirates really like to sing.
That's true.
But why is that first? Hello? Hello?
Yes, this is Navy Headquarters.
Headquarters? Right. Good.
Hello, this is Colonel Nezumi of
Marine Branch 16, Marine Code 00733.
I have a request.
There really is no reason to shout.
I can hear you.
Listen, there's a pirate
who wears a Straw Hat.
He's named Luffy.
Listen, there's a pirate
who wears a Straw Hat.
He's named Luffy.
I hereby declare that he and his four crew
members are enemies of the government.
members are enemies of the government!
Luffy, all right.
They managed to take down the purportedly
invincible fishman
Arlong at his home base!
Based on the grave threat they present,
a large bounty has been
placed on their captain,
Straw Hat Luffy.
Transmitting photograph now.
Roger that.
Huh?
Couldn't you have taken a
better picture than that?
No.
Sorry, sir.
Okay, right after a quick verification,
I'll send it in for approval, sir.
Good!
Don't forget, he's a wanted
pirate, dead or alive!
I want his face on posters
all over the world!
Boy, am I stuffed.
It's nice to not have
to cook for a change.
So how are you feeling, Zoro?
I'll be okay.
I think all I need is
a little bit of rest.
That's good.
Seriously, how much longer
can they keep this up?
It's been three days now.
Nothing wrong with that.
Smoke them if you got them.
Hey, Shanti, where'd you
get that melon you had?
I want to give it a shot.
It isn't polite to talk
with your mouth full.
I don't know.
It was raw ham melon with raw ham on top.
Raw ham melon?
Show me where you found us. I can't.
The whole town is
basically one giant buffet.
Good luck finding it.
He ran off.
Three days of stuffing his face,
so now that my belly is full,
time to dance.
I am Captain Usopp!
I destroyed the strongest
of all the fishmen!
Let's sing about me!
Let's sing!
I am the greatest of friends!
Oh, I'm the best dad to see!
I'm so bored.
I thought you'd be more upset.
Why didn't this happen
before my daddy died?
Why is life so unfair?
That.
I was kind of upset at first.
But I decided just to
think about my future.
What about it?
We were saved by the Straw
Hat guy and his friends.
But tomorrow we have to start all over
again on our own without anybody's help.
We can't forget the past.
But now, it's really
up to us what happens.
There's no one to blame
our problems on anymore.
We can succeed or fail.
It all depends on our choices.
Whining about the past gets us nowhere.
I decided to think that way.
That so? Stop! Ow! Ow! My ghost!
Stop! That hurts! Ow! Stop!
It's no fun if I can't
harass you for being a baby.
So you decided to hurt me
instead, you stupid old punk?
Punk, that's right.
Can you get rid of it?
I'll do my best.
But you do realize this is a tattoo.
I was stupid.
I knew it wouldn't come off.
I don't want anyone to see this.
This...
this awful tattoo.
I'm just pretending, but
it's like he owns me now.
Nami.
Nojiko, what is that?
Oh, you mean this?
It's nothing.
Just a tattoo.
Now I look just like you.
Hey, Doc.
I think I'd like a new tattoo.
Like this.
Look at those two days!
Captain Zabzahn, number 185!
Let's stand as we sing!
Bellamere, your daughters
are strong young women now.
You'd be so proud.
It's like I'm standing
right in front of you again.
We're not going to waste
a single moment now.
So much has been lost.
Everyone has had to make
terrible sacrifices.
Which is why I don't care
if I look like a fool.
I'm happy for the first
time in a long while.
Rohanman!
No food out here.
I'll go back. Be quiet!
Grace?
Did somebody die?
Yes, a long time ago.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I give you to my conveniences.
With my sincere compliments.
No, my darkest con -
My deepest condolences.
Thanks.
Listen, boy.
I know Nami's going away with you.
She has her mind set on becoming a
pirate, and that's dangerous business.
And I'm fine with that.
It can't be helped.
But if any of you ever do anything
to hurt her, I will kill you.
We're not gonna hurt her.
You sure?
I'm sure.
Wow!
What's up with all the food?
Do you two know what today is?
It's the anniversary of the day we met!
We're celebrating the day
you became my daughter.
Hey, don't cry.
It's just a storm so what
if it ruins our crops?
You need to learn to be strong girls
who can smile even during hard times.
Do that and nothing will ever stop you.
Now show me those smiles.
Nami, will you go get the salt?
I see you can draw land maps
now as well as sea charts.
I wanted the book to study navigation.
Navigation as well?
You're going to be a navigator?
That's right.
I'm going to guide ships around
all the oceans of the world.
It'll be great.
And I'll be able to make maps of
all the far-off places I'll go.
So, this island map is a first
step toward realizing your dream.
Is that it?
Yeah!
Well, Bellomere, we finally made it.
It took eight long years,
but we're finally free.
The village and me.
It's just like you told
us when we were children.
Be brave and smile and nothing
will be able to stop you.
It's so true.
Arlong's gone and now everybody
is so happy to be free.
And me.
I'm finally going to leave this island.
But don't worry. I'll be okay.
I'm going with good, strong people.
Like you.
And this last map is
all that I have left to
remind me but none of that
really matters anymore?
Right because now I'll
start again and every
map I draw will be for me and nobody else!
Oh you see this time when I see the
world it will be with all of my friends.
You know that's what I've always wanted.
Anyway I'm just trying to say goodbye.
because I don't know if I'll be back.
I'm going now, okay?
This is the last one, right? Yeah.
Got everything? Yep.
All right, we're stocked
up with everything we need.
I think we're good to go.
You know, we've only been on this
little island for a few days,
but it feels more like a lifetime.
Yeah!
We can't thank you enough for
everything you've done for us,
but we gotta go back to our
regular jobs as bounty hunters.
So this is goodbye.
I hope we get to meet again someday.
See you around.
Goodbye!
Yeah, now it's time for us to get going.
But we can't leave yet.
We gotta wait for Nami.
Well, maybe she's not coming.
What? Why not?
If you tried to hit on her again, I
swear I'll break your freaking neck.
You got it?
Why would I do something like that?
She might not even be coming.
After all, she has achieved her goal.
Nami doesn't have to be a pirate anymore.
She might be better off
if she stayed here on
this island with all
her friends and family.
What about me, damn it?
Without Nami on board,
I have like 98.72 % less reason to stay
with you people on this stupid pirate ship.
Hey, I'm still upset with
you about the raw ham melon.
Why is it Nami here? Don't know.
I haven't seen her anywhere
since this morning.
What?
100 million berries?
She left all the money?
She's not even gonna take some of
it, but she worked so hard to get it.
She'll steal more.
That's what her letter said.
Hmm, there's no changing her
mind once it's made up that girl.
She didn't even give us
a chance to thank her
I don't get it.
Why is she running?
She said to set sail. What?
No, she's planning on leaving us without
letting any of us thank her or say goodbye.
Hey, wait!
Sit still!
Wait! Don't go!
They're leaving! Stop!
At least let us say goodbye!
Nami, don't!
Let us thank you!
Nami!
Come back here!
You can't leave this way!
So, you sure you want to
let her leave like this?
Not my decision.
She does what she wants.
Mommy!
Why?
Huh? No way!
Where's my money?
My wallet's gone! Mine, too!
She stole my money!
My purse is gone!
Thanks a bunch! Damn!
Give it a little brat!
Great.
She hasn't changed a bit.
I'd watch my back.
You lousy pickpockets!
We'll miss you!
Remember what I told you?
You got it!
Goodbye everybody!
I'll miss you. Take care.
I can't believe her!
My little sister Got us good with that one
Be safe Nami
Take a look at this!
What is it, doc?
Nami's bill!
Not exactly!
That girl will never change.
That's her new tattoo!
What's it supposed to be?
A tangerine and a pinwheel
Hey, Genzo, where's your pinwheel?
I don't need it anymore.
I'm off.
Genzo, back off.
Don't get so close to Nami.
I just wanted to see her smile.
Your face is too scary.
It's making her cry.
I can't change my face.
Oh, wait.
I'll keep this on my hat to distract her.
What do you think, little girl?
You're joking, right?
It's just a stupid pinwheel.
There's no way it's going to make her.
I can't believe it.
She's laughing.
I'll say goodbye and squeeze your hand.
I'll say, say I'm alone, but I'll waste.
Now I'm gonna keep you near.
As I drift away, I pray you
watch me as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise, I begin to wonder.
What could be the reason
it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you.
Show me how to catch those feelings,
get them to come back to me.
I'll do what I must because
they're everything I want will be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
and pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make a way.